John Kyle N. Obusan

johnkyleobusan@gmail.com | +63 926 741 0722 | linkedin.com/in/johnkyleo

Summary

A result-oriented professional with a solid grasp of software development methodology and debugging techniques. I have worked on a project where I contributed to the development of new features and have gained experience in documentation to ensure the software quality performance. I have a keen interest in Data Analysis and gained certifications focusing on data visualization software such as Tableau.

Experience

ASSOCIATE SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, ACCENTURE

November 2021 - November 2022

- Responsible for developing a solution based on the client's requirements.
- In charge of gathering and interpreting project's business requirements utilizing a consultative approach.
- Unit test the configuration to ensure any unsuccessful issues are documented and quickly resolved.
- Assists the clients during the implementation period.
- Provides support to the Project Manager and escalates the issues and concerns related to the ongoing project.

DATA ANALYST, GORGEOUS LEGEND BUSINESS SOLUTIONS INC.

September 2019 - February 2020

- In-charge of monitoring and tracking real-time data
- Responsible for collecting web data and analyzing it for business purposes.
- Maintains productivity while managing a good accuracy

Education

DE LA SALLE UNIVERSITY-DASMARIÑAS

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY 2014-2018

Licenses and Certifications

- BASIC TABLEAU SIMPLILEARN
- INTRODUCTION TO DATA ANALYTICS SIMPLILEARN
- DELL BOOMI ASSOCIATE DEVELOPER CERTIFICATION 2022 ACCENTURE
- DELL BOOMI PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPER CERTIFICATE 2022 ACCENTURE
- UKG PRO CERTIFICATION ACCENTURE
- UKG DIMENSION CERTIFICATION ACCENTURE

Skills

• Java • C++ • HTML5 • Data Analytics • Data Processing • Microsoft Office • Communication